FARIDA FARID BABAYEVA

f.babaeva@icloud.com

Date of birth: 26 May, 2001

Address: 214, Abdulla Shaiq str., az1065, Baku, Republic of Azerbaijan

Phone: (+994-12) 595-70-05 Mobile: (+994-50) 705-23-27

Nationality: Azerbaijani

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Education: Administrative Management, Academy of Public Administration

under the President of the Republic of Azerbaijan, GRADUATED

UNEC - Azerbaijan State University of Economics, MBA, Digital

Marketing, GRADUATED

Languages: English – fluent, both written and oral

Russian – fluent, both written and oral

Azeri – native

Computer Skills: Familiar with commonly used word processing, graphics and

database software (Windows, Word Perfect, Microsoft Word,

Microsoft Excel, PowerPoint, etc.)

Summary of professional

experience and skills: Development of project proposals, creation of business plans and

budgets, extensive leadership skills in mentoring and training for programme staff, conducting marketing and business development

strategies, customer service and problem-solving skills

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Dec 2023 – Till now CEO of Mollis Wear Atelier and Showroom (offline, women's

clothing)

April 2020 – Dec 2023 CEO of the Instagram page, online shopping,

maintenance of the online shop's webpage (women's clothing),

Founder of local brand

March 2022 – July 2022 Sales and business development manager, PilatesLife

Dec 2021 – March 2022 Sales Manager in City Business School (Business programs and professional retraining and advanced training courses)

Feb 2021 – June 2021 Rus-Eng translator of PPT lectures of Demography

Oct 2018 – Jan 2020 Freelance mentor on mathematics for secondary school students, taught secondary school course of math for a group of 4 students

May 2018 – May 2019 Freelancer, preparation power point presentations for students of Universities for independent works

EDUCATION

Sept 2015 – May 2018 Lyceum named after academician Zarifa Aliyeva, grades 9-11

Sept 2007 – May 2015 Secondary school N# 60, grades 1-8

TRAINING

May 2021 – May 2022 Business course "Speed" from Ayaz Shabutdinov, Like School,

Moscow, Russia (online)

June 2020 Training on Social Media Marketing (SMM), Feedback School,

Moscow, Russia (online)

July 2020 Training on Copywriting, Feedback School, Moscow, Russia (online)

July 2020 – Aug 2020 Learning session on targeting in Istagram and Facebook, Feedback

School, Moscow, Russia (online)

HOBBY

Reading, chess playing, travelling, swimming, driving, dancing, language learning

MARRITAL STATUS

Single